http://www.ayso76.org/privacy-policy/

How we form Teams
What Division am I in?
Program FAQ
Silent Saturdays
More Programs
Monday Open Practice (MOP)
Coaches
CDC Concussion Awareness Form (Download PDF)
Kids Zone Pledge (Download PDF)
Volunteer Point Program
Referee Code of Conduct (Download PDF)
Field Status / Rainout
Field Maps (Download PDF)
Referee Schedule by Field
Picture Day
Scheduling Spreadsheets
BHUSD Playing Field Rules (Download PDF)
Contact Us
Coach Application (Download PDF)
Player and Parent Commitments (Download PDF)
Fundraising Rules
Coach and Player Selection (Download PDF)
Cup
General
Sportsmanship Cup Information
Field Status / Rainout
Tournament Rules (Download PDF)
Coaches Bulletin
Team Invitation (Download PDF)
Team Registration
Team Application Form (Download PDF)
Team Status
Team Roster Form (Download PDF)
Guest Player Form (Download PDF)
Referees
Referee Schedule
Referee Information
Referee Plan (Download PDF)
Youth Referee Letter (Download PDF)
How we form Teams
What Division am I in?
Program FAQ
Silent Saturdays
More Programs
Monday Open Practice (MOP)
Coaches
CDC Concussion Awareness Form (Download PDF)
Kids Zone Pledge (Download PDF)
Volunteer Point Program
Referee Code of Conduct (Download PDF)
Field Status / Rainout
Field Maps (Download PDF)
Referee Schedule by Field
Picture Day
Scheduling Spreadsheets
BHUSD Playing Field Rules (Download PDF)
Contact Us
Coach Application (Download PDF)
Player and Parent Commitments (Download PDF)
Fundraising Rules
Coach and Player Selection (Download PDF)
Cup
General
Sportsmanship Cup Information
Field Status / Rainout
Tournament Rules (Download PDF)
Coaches Bulletin
Team Invitation (Download PDF)
Team Registration
Team Application Form (Download PDF)
Team Status
Team Roster Form (Download PDF)
Guest Player Form (Download PDF)
Referees
Referee Schedule
Referee Information
Referee Plan (Download PDF)
Youth Referee Letter (Download PDF)
Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement for Region 76 of the American Youth Soccer Organization
Our website is intended to provide information and assist our players and their families as well as volunteers and others who come into contact with our Region. Wewant you to feel comfortable on how we collect and use information from the users.
Region 76 has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.ayso76.org and its associated sites, a list of which is given below.
If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy or want to make any other comment or correction, you should contact webmaster@ayso76.org or write to our Regional Commissioner at PO Box 1761, Beverly Hills, CA 90213.
This policy is clarified to confirm that it applies to users of this site from AYSO Area 1-P and other regions (such as users associated with teams attending the Beverly Hills Sportsmanship Cup). For example, it applies to information submitted concerning players, volunteers and teams participating in Area competitions and the Cup where use is made of our systems. Where appropriate, references to the region should be read as references to Area 1-P.
Legal Status of AYSO
American Youth Soccer Organization (AYSO) is a corporation. Specifically, it is a California nonprofit corporation that is tax exempt under section 501(c)(3) of the United States Internal Revenue Code of 1986, as amended. More information about AYSO is available from the website of the national organization at www.soccer.org.
AYSO operates soccer programs primarily through individual regions. The regions are unincorporated units of AYSO. Region 76 is one such unit. The regions have significant autonomy but they are governed by a variety of rules, regulations and policies established at the national level. When we refer to Region 76 or to "we" in this privacy statement, we refer to the local unit; when we refer to AYSO, we refer to the national organization to which we belong.
Information Collection and Use
This privacy statement explains Region 76's policies on privacy. However, AYSO is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Region 76 initially controls this information and will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Region 76 collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We are subject to control by AYSO and AYSO has the right to use any information collected on our site subject to its own privacy guidelines and policies. Please contact AYSO at 1-800-USA-AYSO or visit www.soccer.org for information on AYSO national policies.
We collect e-mail addresses and other contact information from families and players, primarily but not exclusively through the on-line player registration process. This information is used solely for the purposes of administering our program, registering players to play soccer in our Region and obtaining the appropriate payment for registration and, in the case of volunteers, to inform us of an interest in volunteering. We occasionally send out broadcast e-mail to everyone or large subsets of persons on our e-mail list. These communications invariably relate to soccer or youth sports; in very limited circumstances, it may also be used by us in our sole discretion at the request of the City of Beverly Hills or other government bodies to send messages that we deem relevant to our users. We do not provide the list or contact information to the City or any other third party. A registered user can opt out of receiving email from us by logging in and changing their Family Profile, clicking on their name and checking the opt out box. If you are unable to opt out using this method, we will also remove your name from the list if you ask us by sending an e-mail to remove@ayso76.org. Please note that registering a player on-line will cause the e-mail addresses provided by the registrant to be added to the list, even if the address was previously removed. Individuals with access to any personal information about a player or family member may use such information only for the purposes of administering our program and, without limiting the foregoing, under no circumstances may the information be used for commercial purposes or to solicit for any charity or political cause, unless expressly authorized by our regional commissioner. An individual with such access who contravenes this policy may have access removed and, at the discretion of the regional commissioner or his or her delegate may be.
It is Region 76's policy not to respond to challenge emails. if you use a challenge-based anti-spam system and you have not previously white-listed the ayso76.org and ayso76.net domains or at least commissioner@ayso76.org, registrar@ayso76.org, referee@ayso76.org, coach@ayso76.org, gameschedulers@ayso76.org, refschedulers@ayso76.org and webmaster@ayso76.org, you will not receive any emails from us, including email confirmation of registration and payment. We will not make any effort to contact you.
Registration
Our users currently are not required to register or log in in order to use the public (unrestricted) portion of this website. However, players and volunteers are registered online on a secure site and whether registration occurs on-line or in person, detailed personal information may be gathered and maintained on-line. Information is made available to region administrators on a limited basis through a shared on-line database. It may used only as stated in "Information Collection and Use" above. Until 2005, this was hosted by www.quickbase.com, a unit of Intuit, the maker of Quicken and Quickbooks. The Quickbase database was secure and access to the data was password protected. We also have provided such administrators and certain other volunteers a means of accessing some of this data through a restricted area on the site (see "Additional Information for Registered Users" below). The database is not visible to the public.
In 2005, we moved the restricted portion of our site (www.ayso76.net) to a shared server hosted by CrystalTech and then in April 2006, we completed a move of all our systems to a new dedicated server that we rented and that was operated by a hosting company called APlus. Currently, our data is handled by inLeague LLC, which also programs all of our data-driven online systems. Our data continues to be secure, access to the data continues to require a user name and password and the database is not visible to the public. Categories of users have been expanded to include regional administrators, coaches, referees and parents, with access limited according to the status and specific functions of the user.
Some registration data (not including credit card information) for players and volunteers is passed on to AYSO because all players registered with Region 76 must in turn be registered in a national AYSO database.
Registration information may be requested by the player (if at least 18 years old) or otherwise by the player's parents or legal guardians. Send an e-mail to registrar@ayso76.org or contact the registrar at 310-859-9663, extension 2. We will correct or update information upon request. If a registration is cancelled, we will on request remove the player's information from our on-line database. It is a condition of remaining registered that information will be stored on-line in the manner described above. We cannot adopt special off-line methods of storing player or volunteer data.
Cookies
The site uses cookies primarily to comfort the webmaster when things all get a bit too much (and other times as well). His favorite are the chocolate chip cookies baked by his wife Fiona. Unfortunately, Fiona employs a special kind of tracking cookie which allows her to tell how many the webmaster has eaten, which cookie jar he has had his hand in and other personal information not suitable for public disclosure. The information may be used for purposes of justifying berating him, imposing additional dietary restrictions and other consequences also not suitable for public disclosure. Therefore, the webmaster advises discretion in the use of cookies.
A box of Girl Scout cookies (subject to availability) will be given to the first Beverly Hills AYSO parent or volunteer who confirms having read and understood this new policy.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. We screen our recommended links, however, please be aware that AYSO and Region 76 are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. All forms that contain sensitive information, such as on-line registration of players, are contained on a separate secure site hosted by a well-established company.
Additional Information for Registered Users
Certain users of this site are authorized to access a restricted area on the site that is not available to the general public. In particular, board members, coaches and team administrators and certain other volunteers may have access. Access requires a user name and password issued by the region and may be limited according to the user's function within our region. Registered users are subject to our policies and must comply with directions from the regional webmaster in relation to their use of the restricted portion of the site, including particularly our policy above concerning the use of information to which the user has access through the site. The Region reserves the right at any time to withdraw access rights of Registered users. Registered users should be aware that as part of the security system for the restricted area, a cookie will be set on the user's system to credential that user. This credential cookie is used to allow the user access to those areas of the restricted he or she is entitled to view, and to provide the user the convenience of NOT having to enter an ID and password every time there is a change of screen. On exiting the browser the cookie is deactivated, although a copy may remain on the user's computer.
Notification of Changes
Except in the 90 days following the first posting of this privacy policy on December 1, 2001, if we decide to make non-clerical changes our privacy policy, we will post a prominent link to those changes on our home page for 90 days so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in a different manner. We will use information we collect in accordance with the most recent version of this privacy policy.
This privacy policy was first posted on December 31, 2001. During the 90 days following its posting, we reserve the right to make changes without notice as we refine the policy.
Associated Websites
As noted above, we previously maintained registration data on a private secure site operated by Intuit known as www.quickbase.com. We also continue to maintain historical data concerning certain of our volunteers at the same site, as well as certain other archived information regarding payments (not including credit card numbers). The information is now stored on www.ayso76.net. We collect certain information, including credit card information in connection with credit card payments to our region, through a payment gateway approved by our bank, Union Bank of California. The payment gateways are maintained on secure sites at www.yourpay.com (registration) and www.authorize.net (tournament teams). Only our regional webmaster, regional treasurer and regional registrar and our web developer (and payment gateway personnel) have access to this site. Note that no regional personnel can access actual credit card numbers since we do not store this information - we request such information only for purposes of giving a refund or credit more than 120 days after the date of a registration.
As noted above, we maintain a lot of data on a site we control called www.ayso76.net. This is a temporary domain on a separate server - we will eventually integrate it into www.ayso76.org.
In addition, AYSO maintains an on-line player and volunteer database with extensive and developing functionalities that is now available for use by our region. This database is found at www.eayso.org. We make use of the functionalities and capabilities of the eAYSO and this may increase in the future. For more information, visit the eAYSO site.
Choice/Opt-Out
If you do not wish to receive e-mails from us, please log in, go to My Account, click on Family Profile and click on your name. Then click the opt out button. You can also simply sent an e-mail to remove@ayso76.org. Make sure that we can see your correct e-mail address and that you identify yourself.
However, we do not permit volunteers - coaches, referees and team administrators to opt out of receiving emails. We use your email address, and we may in future use your phone or PDA number, to send written communications with you that our relevant to your service as a volunteer. If nevertheless you do not wish to receive such communications from us, you will first need to resign as a volunteer by contacting the appropriate regional administrator (the relevant division directors if you are a coach of one or more teams, your coach or the division director if you are a team administrator, the referee administrator if you are a referee, or the regional commissioner if you are a volunteer in any other position).
Individuals with particular privacy concerns should contact the webmaster at webmaster@ayso76.org.
